<system>
  <title>BOSS</title>
  <acronym-expansion>
    Boosting Open Source Software
  </acronym-expansion>
  <short-description>
    Software engineering manager for project management
  </short-description>
  <medium-description>
    BOSS coordinates the software development of our internal
    codebases, the applications that we are writing to either
    effectively glue together external codebases as in most cases or
    as mostly independent projects (like Gourmet).  BOSS converses
    with Architect to coordinate development of icodebases with
    respect to overall goals, and RADAR and Machiavelli to provide a
    project development simulator for use in reasoning about other
    projects, and in general, to answer software development
    questions.  BOSS also automates many of the aspects of writing
    codebases.
  </medium-description>
  <long-description>
  <ul>
    <li>
      It is an agent,  which communicates over (UniLang/FL/etc.) which
      is responsible  for several tasks related to  source and project
      management/development.
    </li>
    <li>
      Handle setup of preferences for tools used in creating software.
    </li>
    <li>
      Ability   to    create   project,   or   to    run   tests   and
      recommend/implement  changes to project  structure to  make them
      compatible with our development model.
    </li>
    <li>
      Have  an  update-rc.d like  system  that  handles the  following
      things: It scans  a project for information about  hooks that it
      must register with the system  BEFORE they get packaged, so that
      we can test,  develop and use these features,  without having to
      build and install the package for every single change, i.e.
    </li>
    <li>
      Yet, when the package is installed, it intelligent selects which
      hooks ought to  be activated between the package  and the source
      system, on certain criteria, and allows hot swapping.
    </li>
    <li>
      Create an FRDCSA distribution CD or DVD on demand.  Perhaps, use
      KNOPPIX as a starter.
    </li>
  </ul>
  </long-description>
  <todolist>
    <todo>
      Make sure the Emacs source file is autoloaded from Emacs
    </todo>
    <todo>Make sure the binaries are linked to in the path.</todo>
    <todo>Make sure the documentation is indexed.</todo>
    <todo>Make sure the Perl Modules are in @INC.</todo>
  <recommends>
    openafs-client
  </recommends>

  <synonyms>
    Software  Engineer,  Developer,  Leader, Boss,  Manager,  Software
    Engineering Manager, Project Management
  </synonyms>
  </todolist>
    <links>
    <link>http://asg.web.cmu.edu/isam/</link>
  </links>
</system>